I want the truth about Tee and you.
We're friends. I haven't broken up with Jeen yet.
But… who did you make this cake for?
He is a very adorable person.
Fuse, I bought you a cake.
Yesterday, there was really nothing.
So, that's what you want to explain.
Where are you going after school?
How about getting something to eat?
Around here?
Is there anything around here to eat?
Same place as usual?
Fuse.
How are you feeling?
I feel better now.
Tee helped me to apply a cold compress.
Thanks.
I'm leaving.
Hey, it's good that you're okay.
If you love me,
you must not push me away.
Fuse, I bought you a cake.
Why does Robert think that he did something wrong?
Don't you think he cares Bas way too much?
So, that's what you want to explain.
Why did you tell me about it?
Ugh!
Are you okay?
What has gotten into you?
How cool.
How am I wrong?
She's my girlfriend though.
Why is he mad at me?
Tee.
I was not talking about you.
I was talking about Robert Sae-tang.
Hey.
What brings them here?
I think…
They're here for the basketball match meeting.
Hey, get off of me.
Huh?
I gotta go.
What?
Wait for me, daddy.
Don't be nosy.
It's okay. You can go with me.
Um.
EstWit forever.
Go.
Let's go.
Do you want me to stay with you?
Hey, I'm good.
I'm leaving.
You got this, Robert Sae-tang.
Hey.
That's not me.
What are you talking about? I'm leaving.
[Yok.]
Hey.
Let go.
You're cute, by the way.
Fuse.
Excuse me.
I'd like one scoop of coconut milk ice cream, please.
Fuse.
What's wrong?
Yesterday…
Our face…
Hey.
Ouch.
Ah.
But I'm the one who pushed you.
It's me who startled you.
But I didn't mean it.
Then it's fine.
You pushed me so hard.
You totally scared me.
You're dramatic.
I'm not.
I think if our lips actually touched,
you would punch me.
Well, I'm sorry.
I had a lot on my mind.
You don't have to be sorry.
It's weird…
if you don't push me away.
Why?
Haven't you heard of this?
I've heard people say that…
if you want to know who loves you, lean in close.
If they don't flinch, there is a chance.
But you pushed me so hard.
Where did he go?
Thank you.
Thank you for treating me.
It's on me next time.
Um, see you later.
If you want to know who loves you, lean in close.
If they don't flinch, there is a chance.
Tee.
What brings you here?
Buying stuff.
Is your ride here yet?
Can I come with you?
Tee, we need to talk.
Tee.
Does your house really have a ghost?
Hey.
Tee.
Tee, we need to talk.
What's going on?
I'm your friend.
Like you want me to be.
Can we go back to what we used to be?
What we used to be.
What did we use to be?
Like before?
That we're not close to each other?
Or like what we are now?
I think I can't go back to that.
You should go back.
I won't.
Go back.
You should go back.
No.
Go back.
Tee.
Did you bring a friend?
Hello, I'm Fuse.
So,
Fuse…
is friends with Tee.
But you're in different classes?
Yes.
I'm in class 10.
And Tee…
is in class 13.
How did you get close to each other?
Actually, we're not close.
But Tee always shows up and helps me.
The key is inside my bag.
And no one is home.
How about a sleepover at my house?
Whenever something bothers me,
he's always by my side.
Hey.
A lot of things brought us closer.
And I'm glad to be close with Tee.
A good relationship...
is not a coincidence.
I have to go.
Goodbye, Tim.
Yimwan.
Yes, Mr. Tim.
Let's go.
To where?
So, what are you doing here?
I'm here because I know.
I know what you saw yesterday.
Tee.
So, what are you doing here?
I'm here because I know.
I know what you saw yesterday.
I'm sorry…
if I hurt your feelings.
But there was really nothing.
Are you gonna say that…
you don't know how I feel about you?
Or you do know it…
but just playing with me?
It's my fault.
For thinking I had a chance.
About yesterday, it's not your fault at all.
But I think I need to step away.
Can you not step away?
I don't want you to go anywhere.
I don't know…
how I feel either.
And I don't know…
how I feel about you either.
But I don't want it to be like this.
I want us to get close again.
As friends?
If I kissed you right now,
would we still be friends?
I told you…
not to try things like this jokingly.
Because I actually like you.
Alright.
I know it.
You're so unfair.
I was actually going to let you go.
I'm sorry.
You know it, right?
If you hold me back,
I can't go anywhere.
I'm really sorry.
Why are you looking at me?
Because you're cute.
Likes a dog.
Woof-woof.
What?
Hey.
Tee, what are you doing?
Try barking, woof-woof.
What?
Woof-woof.
No.
Hey.
Tee.
Don't do that.
Hey.
Tee.
Ah.
Tee, don't do that.
You really did this, huh?
You asked for it.
Hey, don't.
You did this to me.
Don't. Don't.
Huh?
Don't do that.
Okay.
Tee.
Does this shirt look too nerdy on me?
Nerdy? You're absolutely fine.
Really?
Um.
What about the pants? Are they weird?
No, you're overthinking it.
Come here.
Who says nerdy? You're really handsome.
Really?
Hello, Tim.
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
Tim.
I'm not going to school today. I'm lazy.
Hey, can you really say that?
That's good.
You should take a break.
If you're lazy, then don't go to school.
I already told Yimwan to prepare breakfast for you.
I'll finish it all.
Fuse likes Korean food.
Right.
I forgot to tell her to prepare Korean food.
Yimwan.
Yes?
Could you prepare Korean food, please?
Of course.
That's fine.
We'll eat out.
Hey.
I can eat it.
No.
Tee.
Take my credit card.
Just let him know what you want to eat.
Okay.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Um.
Tim is so generous.
Surprise.
What a coincidence.
My school is off.
And also your school?
Dang, Tim is so generous.
Yeah, he's a big spender.
Um.
Whoever dates him must be so lucky, right?
Why did you say like that?
Eh?
Does he have a partner yet?
I don't know.
I guess…
he's already taken.
Because he's incredibly handsome.
[Tim 1 - 0 Tee.]
Handsome?
I'm more handsome than him.
[Tim 1 - 1 Tee.]
But he's productive.
[Tim 2 - 1 Tee.] I'm also clever.
[Tim 2 - 2 Tee.]
But Tim is kind.
[Tim 3 - 2 Tee.]
I'm also kind.
[Tim 3 - 3 Tee.]
And Tim also…
Enough.
Don't look at others when you're with me.
I won't let it slide, even though that person is Tim.
Whoa.
Wait and see.
Ten years later,
I'll be ten times better than Tim.
Alright.
For now, keep his credit card safely.
Or we'll end up with nothing to eat.
Okay.
Let's go.
There is one thing…
that I'm definitely better than Tim.
What is it?
My hips.
That's disgusting.
You look like an old person.
Old person?
Look at my hips.
I'm out.
What are we having?
When did I tell you that…
I like Korean food?
So, it will just be the two of us.
Why does it have to be only the two of us?
I just want to be with you.
Tee, someone might see us.
Are you blushing?
No way.
You're blushing, right?
I told you, I'm not blushing.
Does it look like I'm blushing?
[In Chinese] Excuse me.
[In Chinese] You're so handsome./ Can I take a picture of you?
Can you understand him?
I don't know what he said.
Sorry, what did you say again?
Uh…
Excuse…
Excuse me.
I'm…
I'm a Chinese photographer.
You…
You're very handsome.
Can I take a picture of you?
Go ahead.
Will it take long?
[In Chinese] It won't take so long. Only five minutes.
It won't take long.
I'm afraid you'll wait for a long time.
You should do it.
I also want to see the pictures.
I'll do it.
But please don't take it too long.
[In Chinese] Thank you.
[In Chinese] This way, please.
[In Chinese] One, two, three.
[in Chinese]One, two, three.
Is he a celebrity?
I'd better take his photo.
In case he's actually a celebrity.
Is he handsome?
He just has fair skin.
Asian look.
And tall.
Just like me.
Let's take a picture.
Can I take a picture with you?
The photographer will give it as a gift.
Thank you.
Find the answer of…
Seven minus two to the power of N plus two minus/ three point two to the power of n minus four,
Is it him who you met yesterday?
all over four plus two to the power of n minus one/ plus two to the power of n minus three.
Hey, you follow him right away?
Yeah, it's just following the cheerleaders.
So, will you follow all of them?
Nah.
Huh?
Why did you take a picture?
Because the person is beautiful.
Huh?
No, I mean the person is beautiful and the light as well.
Can you take a pic of me like that too?
Okay.
Frame, do it properly.
I'm not in the mood to take pictures.
Teacher, I have a question.
Yes, go ahead.
If we want to stay with someone…
Want to stay close and smell his scent all the time…
What should I do?
I think that person might be…
a very important person for you, Frame.
If I were you, I would tell them.
Thank you.
What?
I just want to thanks the teacher.
Teacher, may I go to the bathroom?
I feel a bit queasy.
Okay.
Thank you.
How many dishes you ordered?
You can have them all.
Can I take a pic for IG story first?
Whoa.
It looks yummy.
If you finish taking photos, can I eat them now?
Not these.
I mean this.
(Fuse) Tee.
(Tee) Ough.
Surprise.
What a coincidence.
My school is off.
And also your school?
Uh…
I didn't know at first.
But I saw your IG story so I came over to look.
I didn't expect to see Tee here.
Right.
About the other day,
I'm sorry.
Were you surprised?
I saw you just put a cake and ran away.
I told you we should be careful.
I'm too embarrassed to face Tee now.
Wow, you guys ordered quite a lot.
Can I join you guys?
Of course.
I'm joking. I'm meeting my friends.
Just came to say hi.
I gotta go.
Maybe next time. Bye.
Tee.
Are you okay?
[Fuse] Take it./ [Tee] Ouch.
Ouch.
Tee, are you fighting back?
So what?
I'll give in to you just for today.
Ouch.
Tee.
It hurts.
You said you'll give in to me.
Out of quota.
Ouch.
That hurts.
Fine, I'll let you bite me.
Tee!
Tee. Ouch.
Did you actually bite me?
Here.
Come here.
Come closer, quickly.
Closer.
Here.
Come here.
Come closer, quickly.
That's too far.
Hurry up, come closer.
Hey, I won't let you bite it.
I told you not to talk to me at school.
Don't leave yet.
I want to recharge.
Fuse is skipping school without telling me.
He left me at school.
Are you on IG all day?
You should stay at school.
Why would you go there to be a third wheel?
A third wheel?
Did he go there with Jeen?
Hey.
Tell me.
I.
Won't.
Tell me. I die to know it.
Stop it.
I might be dead in the game.
Tell me.
Wit, damn.
Hey, tell me.
Wit, don't do that.
Tell me.
Wit.
Stop it.
Tell me.
Wit.
What's up, Book?
You came all the way here for me?
You miss me, I know.
I understand. You can't live without me.
Ouch.
So full of yourself.
It hurts.
Ouch, it hurts.
Stop being dramatic.
Ouch.
I told you not to talk to me at school.
Can't we talk here?
Nobody is here.
You're not allowed.
Hey.
Don't leave yet.
I want to recharge.
Recharge?
Frame.
I'm fully charged.
Got energy for the next class.
Um.
I'll wait and see.
Book.
Are you starting to like me yet?
That's cute, I want one.
I'll buy it for you.
Really?
Yeah.
Aww.
You're the best.
What about we put on matching hats?
This is mine.
And yours is…
This one.
Try put it on.
Shall we buy neckties?
Um.
This one.
Which one is better?
Are you okay?
About what?
About Jeen?
Actually, I'm not okay.
I don't understand.
If she has somebody else,
why doesn't she break up with me?
Why did she try to make up with me?
Fuse!
Can you hold them for me, please?
Sup, guys.
Is your band playing as well?
Yes, today is the last day.
Okay, I'll look forward to it.
Everybody.
Yes?
Is Fuse handsome?
Yes.
But he's not only handsome.
He can sing as well.
He'll show it to you guys.
Rodtang, I can't sing.
Just sing, like you're singing at home.
Let Look sing instead. I'm looking forward to watching.
Fine, wait right here then.
Okay.
Hello, we're from C.P.A College.
I'm exhausted.
Me too.
But I think it's great.
Really great.
Where are you going?
Khao Yai!
Do you think we will share a bed?
Why?
So we can do things more easily.
So, you posted pics…
just to get people to like you?
If that's all you want, you can deactivate your account.
I can do it for you.
I told you.
If you want me to stay, I won't go anywhere.
Will you stay with me forever then?